<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Shubham Tatvamasi</title>
    <link>https://shubhamtatvamasi.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Shubham Tatvamasi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2017 12:21:21 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://shubhamtatvamasi.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Photography</title>
      <link>https://shubhamtatvamasi.com/projects/photography/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2017 12:21:21 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shubhamtatvamasi.com/projects/photography/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes I take pictures. This project is about the pictures I take. Sometimes, they are pictures of cats.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Design</title>
      <link>https://shubhamtatvamasi.com/projects/design/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2017 12:21:16 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shubhamtatvamasi.com/projects/design/</guid>
      <description>This theme was designed by Vicky Lai. Go on, explore! 💪
If you want to use it for your website, check out the section at the bottom of the main page. 👍</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Writing</title>
      <link>https://shubhamtatvamasi.com/projects/writing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2017 12:21:11 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shubhamtatvamasi.com/projects/writing/</guid>
      <description>Aromatic aroma con panna, crema so coffee robust coffee barista, café au lait trifecta that strong blue mountain cortado aftertaste. Aroma extraction french press, skinny sweet, blue mountain cup roast barista, beans, extra cappuccino mug crema strong.
To go viennese cream to go, flavour, so mocha as, carajillo iced et a siphon froth. Aged, eu, cup, brewed aroma kopi-luwak, coffee, id viennese french press brewed grounds acerbic froth. Decaffeinated acerbic, spoon beans seasonal, french press café au lait mazagran roast chicory, pumpkin spice galão as fair trade, dark irish cup ristretto half and half whipped shop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hipster</title>
      <link>https://shubhamtatvamasi.com/blog/hipster/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2017 11:58:39 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shubhamtatvamasi.com/blog/hipster/</guid>
      <description>Occupy mlkshk kale chips woke, listicle locavore next level fingerstache glossier aesthetic man braid before they sold out kitsch prism. Cred copper mug freegan, flannel YOLO single-origin coffee skateboard artisan four loko church-key man bun. Synth literally gastropub, kombucha chillwave helvetica offal truffaut church-key freegan pop-up gentrify narwhal. Kombucha viral vexillologist green juice. Slow-carb hoodie mumblecore tumeric tattooed meditation, lo-fi fap cred affogato forage whatever austin. Shabby chic direct trade migas, brunch gochujang sriracha chambray fanny pack 8-bit mustache letterpress.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Startup Ipsum</title>
      <link>https://shubhamtatvamasi.com/blog/startup-ipsum/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2017 12:04:06 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shubhamtatvamasi.com/blog/startup-ipsum/</guid>
      <description>SpaceTeam affordances quantitative vs. qualitative SpaceTeam physical computing earned media thinker-maker-doer pair programming. Bootstrapping pitch deck physical computing driven cortado human-centered design innovate human-centered design driven. Grok pitch deck fund pitch deck sticky note affordances minimum viable product integrate paradigm viral iterate. Driven fund thought leader personas workflow SpaceTeam viral pair programming physical computing intuitive 360 campaign latte bootstrapping minimum viable product. Bootstrapping physical computing responsive pitch deck SpaceTeam parallax long shadow pitch deck bootstrapping ideate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coffee Ipsum</title>
      <link>https://shubhamtatvamasi.com/blog/coffee-ipsum/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2017 12:04:16 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shubhamtatvamasi.com/blog/coffee-ipsum/</guid>
      <description>Aromatic aroma con panna, crema so coffee robust coffee barista, café au lait trifecta that strong blue mountain cortado aftertaste. Aroma extraction french press, skinny sweet, blue mountain cup roast barista, beans, extra cappuccino mug crema strong. Americano caffeine white, con panna saucer sit, con panna eu, carajillo aftertaste kopi-luwak, body aftertaste cup single origin café au lait saucer. Macchiato java sweet arabica, turkish cup, eu flavour mug extraction white cortado saucer est white brewed instant, rich, barista breve cappuccino barista organic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://shubhamtatvamasi.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2017 13:23:28 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shubhamtatvamasi.com/contact/</guid>
      <description>I am always searching for new things to learn, and connecting with awesome people,
If you think you are the one feel free to contact me anytime you like.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://shubhamtatvamasi.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2017 13:19:25 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shubhamtatvamasi.com/about/</guid>
      <description>This is my Introduction:
I am Blockchain Architect and Ethereum open source contributor, I have been working on Blockchain technologies since 2015 onwards. I entered into Blockchain space because I truly believe that this is the future of Internet and I want to make this a reality. My life’s goal is to build a fully decentralized world where everything is transparent and full of trust.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Technical</title>
      <link>https://shubhamtatvamasi.com/technical/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2017 13:19:25 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shubhamtatvamasi.com/technical/</guid>
      <description>Some Technologies I play with:
Programming Languages: JavaScript, Python, GoLang, Solidity
Frameworks: Node.js, Express.js, React, Angular, Django, Flask
Blockchain: Ethereum, Hyperledger, IPFS, Web3.js, Remix, Truffle
Databases: MySQL, SQLite, MongoDB
Linux: Ubuntu, LinuxMint, CentOS
DevOps: Docker, Kubernetes, OpenStack, Jenkins, Nginx, Apache
Cloud: AWS, GCP, Azure, Heroku
AI: Kubeflow, Jupyterhub, Jupyter Notebook
Tools: Git, Github, Gitlab, Jira, Trello</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>